Guide to the Vice President for Student Affairs records, 1923-[ongoing] UA.09.02.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession A74-78, 1
  - United Fund, 1965-1968 (Box 20)
  - United Nations (Day), 1965-1966 (Box 20)
  - "A University Center": Spring 1963 proposal (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: 2 campus situation, E. H. Hopkins, 1963 (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: 1963 program for Trustees (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: 1964 minutes (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: excerpts from Statements of Union Purpose (Associations of Colleges & Universities), undated (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: floor plans, undated (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: July 1964 Report, 1964 July (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: miscellaneous reports, undated (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: notice of meetings, 1963-1964 (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: other institutions, undated (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: proposal for a Woman's College Center, 1964 (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: questionnaires, 1963 (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: report to Educational Facilities Committee, 1964 May (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: Student Building Commission, Nursing School, undated (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: Student Union Expansion proposal, 1959 November (Box 20)
  - University Center Committee: Time Magazine Excerpts, 1964 December (Box 20)
  - University Council on Research: travel budget regulations, 1968 (Box 20)
  - University of North Carolina, 1965-1966 (Box 20)
  - University Planning Committees, 1962-1968 (Box 20)
  - University Planning Committees: reports, 1962-1963 (Box 20)
  - University Union, 1969 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Cinematic Arts, 1966-1968 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Drama, 1965-1967 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Educative Involvement, 1964-1969 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Graphic Arts, 1967 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Major Attractions (Pledger case), 1969 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Major Speakers, 1966-1968 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Major Speakers (Adam Clayton Powell), 1968 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Performing Arts, 1966-1967 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Special Projects, 1969 (Box 21)
  - University Union: committees: Facilities Council, 1967-1970 (Box 21)
  - University Union Planning Committee (DUUPC), 1968 (Box 21)
  - University Union Retreat, 1969 September 13 (Box 21)
  - University Research Council, 1969 (Box 21)
  - University Weekends, 1965-1968 (Box 21)
  - Visiting Resident Scholar Committee, 1968 (Box 21)
  - Visitors, 1964-1969 (Box 21)
  - Volunteers in Service to America (VISTA), 1965-1968 (Box 21)
  - Voting Age Council of North Carolina, 1967 (Box 21)
  - Walks: building of diagonal walks for quadrangle correspondence, 1963 (Box 21)
  - West Campus Community Council, 1969 (Box 21)
  - Woman's College, 1963-1968 (Box 21)
  - Woman's Student Government Association, 1965-1966 (Box 21)
  - World University Service, 1969 (Box 21)
  - YMCA-YWCA, 1960-1968 (Box 21)
  - YMCA Treasurer's Report, 1964-1967 (Box 21)
- Accession A80-35, 6
  This accession includes a small amount of materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Files include correspondence, reports, and other materials on the Publications Board, various student groups and activities, and other topics. Materials primarily date from 1969-1974.
  - Association of College & University Concert managers, circa 1967 (Box 33)
  - Betterments Screening Committee, 1970 (Box 33)
  - Bicycle Club, 1971 (Box 33)
  - Blazers: correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 33)
  - Blue Jeans: constitution, 1968 (Box 33)
  - Business manager, 1969-1973 (Box 33)
  - Campus Community Council, 1971-1973 (Box 33)
  - Duke Campus Crusade for Christ, 1971 (Box 33)
  - Durham Chamber of Commerce: Recreation Committee, 1973 (Box 33)
  - Studies, Reports, Speeches, 1974-1975; 3 folders (Box 34)
  - Durham Emergency Telephone Service, 1970 (Box 34)
  - Town Men's Club, 1970 (Box 34)
  - University Weekends, Steering Committee for, 1969 (Box 34)
  - Visitor: Elliot L. Richardson, Secretary of Health, Education, & Welfare, 1971 February 28-1971 March 1 (Box 34)
  - Housing: Hanes Annex, 1971-1972 (Box 34)
  - Publications Board (1 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 34)
  - Publications Board (2 of 2), 1970-1972 (Box 35)
  - Publications Board: petitions, 1972 (Box 35)
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1970-1971 (Box 35)
  - Omega House, 1972 (Box 35)
  - Town House Apartments, 1970-1974 (Box 35)
  - Humanities Council, 1973 (Box 35)
  - Human Sexuality Workshop, 1973 (Box 35)
  - Listening Post, 1970 (Box 35)
  - Mass Media Communications Development group, 1972 (Box 35)
  - Media Center, 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - National Prayer Breakfast, 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Durham Police, 1969 (Box 35)
  - Public Safety Office, 1969-1973 (Box 35)
  - Public Safety Office, 1969-1973 (Box 191)
    FERPA restricted until 2043.
  - Radio Council, 1969-1971 (Box 35)
  - Public Safety Committee: campus sub-committee, 1972-1973 (Box 35)
  - Rugby Club, 1972-1974 (Box 35)
  - Southern Student Organizing Committee, 1969 (Box 35)
  - Large Staff Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 35)
  - Small Staff Meetings, 1971-1974 (Box 36)
  - Special University Ceremonies Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
  - Student Activities, 1969-1973 (Box 36)
  - Student Activities ("under Joe Martin"), 1964-1970 (Box 36)
  - Community Showcase program, 1972 (Box 36)
  - Community Change program, 1972 (Box 36)
  - Student Activities Loan Fund, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - Student Activities office: financial, 1969-1973 (Box 36)
- Accession A80-201, 3
  This accession contains materials on student fraternities from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Files include information on fraternity activities and status. Much of the materials in this series are restricted under FERPA.
  - Alpha Tau Omega Fraternity, 1953-1975 (Box 188)
    FERPA restricted until 2045.
  - Beta Theta Pi Fraternity, 1948-1971 (Box 188)
    FERPA restricted until 2041.
  - Delta Sigma Phi Fraternity, 1947-1972 (Box 188)
    FERPA restricted until 2042.
  - Delta Tau Delta Fraternity, 1947-1971 (Box 188)
  - Gamma Beta Phi Society, 1965-1966 (Box 26)
  - Kappa Alpha Fraternity, 1949-1972 (Box 188)
  - Kappa Sigma Fraternity, 1947-1972 (Box 189)
  - Lambda Chi Alpha Fraternity, 1948-1977 (Box 189)
    FERPA restricted until 2047.
  - Omega Psi Phi Fraternity, 1974-1974 (Box 26)
  - Phi Delta Theta Fraternity, 1947-1972 (Box 189)
  - Phi Gamma Tau Fraternity (local fraternity: formerly Lambda Chi Alpha), 1968-1971 (Box 26)
  - Phi Kappa Psi Fraternity, 1960-1972 (Box 189)
  - Phi Kappa Sigma Fraternity, 1951-1972 (Box 189)
  - Phi Kappa Fraternity, 1959-1972 (Box 189)
    May contain some Phi Kappa Sigma material
  - Phi Kappa Alpha Fraternity, 1960-1975 (Box 189)
  - Pi Kappa Phi Fraternity, 1969-1973 (Box 189)
  - Phi Psi Fraternity, 1969 (Box 26)
  - Psi Upsilon Fraternity (Chi Delta chapter), 1968-1973 (Box 26)
  - Sigma Alpha Epsilon Fraternity, 1960-1972 (Box 190)
  - Sigma Chi Fraternity, 1960-1974 (Box 190)
    FERPA restricted until 2044.
  - Sigma Nu Fraternity, 1953-1972 (Box 190)
  - Sigma Phi Epsilon Fraternity, 1953-1972 (Box 190)
  - Tau Epsilon Phi Fraternity, 1954-1972 (Box 190)
  - Theta Chi Fraternity, 1949-1969 (Box 26)
  - Fraternities: discriminating clauses (other institutions), 1967 (Box 26)
  - Fraternities: desegregation, 1965 (Box 26)
  - Residential Judicial System, 1972-1973 (Box 26)
  - Residential Judicial System: appeals, 1975 (Box 26)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1971 (Box 26)
  - Zeta Beta Tau Fraternity, 1949-1972 (Box 190)
- Accession A81-113, 2
  This series includes materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Materials include correspondence, reports, memorandums, and other materials on the Duke Players guest directors, Chapel activities, and other topics.
  - Chamber of Commerce: Travel & Convention Task Force, 1970-1971 (Box 22)
  - Council on Leaders & Specialists, 1970-1973 (Box 22)
  - Council on Youth Opportunity, 1970-1972 (Box 22)
  - Draft, 1969-1972 (Box 22)
  - Durham Civic & Cultural Center Commission, 1970 (Box 22)
  - Durham Human Relations Commission, 1973 (Box 22)
  - Durham Motel-Hotel, 1974 (Box 22)
  - Durham Research Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 22)
  - Office of Community Relations: Director, 1972-1976 (Box 22)
  - Campus Christian Ministry Study, 1972 (Box 22)
  - Campus Ministry, 1971-1972 (Box 22)
  - Chapel: Carillon, 1964-1973 (Box 22)
  - Chapel: budget, 1971-1973 (Box 22)
  - Chapel Sunday Policy, Administrative Committee on, 1966 (Box 22)
  - Duke University Christian Council, 1967-1975 (Box 22)
  - Presbyterian Campus Christian Life Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 22)
  - Religious Activities, 1968-1974 (Box 22)
  - Duke United Ministry, 1970-1975 (Box 23)
  - Chapel Use Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Choral Activities: Oratorio Performance, 1964-1970 (Box 23)
  - Committee to Honor James T. Cleland, 1973-1974 (Box 23)
  - Religious Activities Study, 1971-1972 (Box 23)
  - United Ministry: Executive Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 23)
  - United Ministry: Joint Executive Committee, 1970-1972 (Box 23)
  - United Ministry: Joint Executive Committee minutes, 1970-1973 (Box 23)
  - Duke Players, 1970-1973; 2 folders (Box 23)
  - Duke Players, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Duke Players, 1974-1976 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Constitution, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: fundraising committee, 1972 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Director: Clinton Atkinson, 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Robert Brink, Cat on a Hot Tin Roof, 1972-1972 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Donald M. Colucci, 1969-1970 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Robert Fisher (musical directors): "Jacques Brel", 1974 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Ella Gerber: "Madwoman", 1969-1973 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: John Cullum, 1974-1975 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: William M. Hardy: "J.B.", 1972 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: William M. Hardy: "The Crucible", 1971 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Philip Lawrence: "Little Murders", 1968-1973 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Philip Lawrence: "The Corinthian", 1973-1974 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: John Miller: "Rhinoceros", 1971 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: John Morrow: "The Tempest", 1972 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Kent Paul: "Hostage", 1967-1973 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Shawn Smith: "Streetcar Named Desire", 1973 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: Laura Stuart: "The Corinthian", 1974 (Box 24)
  - Duke Players: Resident Managing Technical Director: Scott Parker, 1971-1974 (Box 24)
  - Class chair endowed, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Commencement, 1970-1973 (Box 24)
  - Dean of Students, 1972-1974 (Box 24)
  - Faculty Club, 1969-1974 (Box 24)
  - Duke University 50th Anniversary, 1975 April (Box 24)
  - Ford Fountain, 1970-1971 (Box 24)
  - Gladstone Associates, 1970-1971 (Box 24)
  - Graduate Student Association: correspondence, 1969-1973 (Box 25)
  - Graduate Student Association: newsletter, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Housing, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
  - Personal Policies, 1971-1973 (Box 25)
  - Correspondence: WJ Griffith, miscellaneous, 1968-1973 (Box 25)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: selection committee, 1972-1974 (Box 25)
  - Duke Players: Guest Directors: selection committee, 1972-1974 (Box 190)
    Personnel restricted until 2044.
  - University Chaplain: Search Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 25)
  - Lady Austin: Assistant Minister of the University, personnel file, 1971-1974 (Box 25)
  - Assistant University Chaplain: Elmer Hall: personnel file, 1967-1973 (Box 25)
  - Personnel: Religious Activities, 1967-1972 (Box 25)
  - Chapel Organist: Floyd B. Gulick, jr.: personnel, 1968-1972 (Box 25)
  - Choral Activities: Paul Young: personnel, 1956-1974 (Box 25)
  - Assistant Director of Chapel Music: George Ritchie: personnel, 1969-1973 (Box 25)
  - Choral Activities: James Benjamin Smith: personnel, 1964-1975 (Box 25)
  - Assistant Chapel Organist: David Hurd: personnel, 1972-1973 (Box 25)
  - Joyce Painter: Accompanist: personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 25)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa handbooks, 1957-1970; 3 folders (Box 26)
- Accession A82-31, 9
  This series includes materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President of Student Affairs. Included are materials related to the ten year reunion of the class of 1950, which William Griffith was involved in planning. Other personal materials were removed from this series and returned to William Griffith.
  - Class of 1950 Reunion, 1958-1960 (Box 106)
  - Class of 1950 Reunion 1960, circa 1960; 2 folders (Box 107)
  - The Duke Vigil: personal narrative, 1968 (Box 107)
- Accession A82-113, 4
  This series includes a small amount of materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President of Student Affairs. Files include correspondence, reports, memorandums, and other materials related to student activities, student regulations, and other topics.
  - Beta Theta Pi Fraternity, 1970-1980 (Box 190)
    FERPA restricted until 2050.
  - Equal Opportunity Office, 1971-1979; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Expediter's Group, 1976-1979 (Box 27)
  - Explorer's Club, 1975-1977 (Box 27)
  - Griffith, William J.: miscellaneous correspondence, 1978 August; 2 folders (Box 27)
  - Griffith, William J.: invitations, 1971-1981 (Box 28)
  - Housing: Committee on Student Housing at Duke University, 1969-1970 (Box 28)
  - Housing: Durham Motor Inn, 1977-1978 (Box 28)
  - Housing: student problems, 1975-1977; 2 folders (Box 191)
    FERPA restriction until 2047
  - Movement for Shared Authority, undated (Box 28)
  - Duke Model United Nations Group, 1973 (Box 28)
  - Intramural Board, 1971-1980; 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Joe College Weekend, 1971-1977 (Box 28)
  - National Leadership Institute, 1971-1974 (Box 28)
  - New American Movement, 1975 (Box 28)
  - New Curriculum (Subcommittee on English), 1974 (Box 28)
  - Provost Group, 1969-1978 (Box 28)
  - Residential Staff, 1973-1979 June; 2 folders (Box 29)
  - Student-Faculty-Administration Council, 1968-1970 (Box 29)
  - Student resources: full-scale student survey, 1970 (Box 29)
  - Trespass Regulations, 1970-1971 (Box 29)
  - "United Campus Community Council": proposal, 1971 (Box 29)
  - WDBS radio station, 1969-1974 (Box 29)
  - Woman's College, 1969-1969 (Box 29)
- Accession A84-98, 5
  This series includes materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Files include reports, correspdonce, and other materials related to student organizations (particularly constitutions), the Publications Board, student health insurance providers, and other topics.
  - The Cornell Daily Sun, 1969 April (Box 29)
  - Constitution: Associated Student Governments of the USA, 1965 January 6 (Box 29)
  - Constitution: Interfraternity Council, 1965 March 3 (Box 29)
  - Constitution: Men's Student Government Association, 1965 April 6 (Box 29)
  - Constitution: Nurses' Student Government Association, 1964 February 5 (Box 29)
  - Constitution: Student organizations, A-D, undated (Box 29)
  - Constitution: Student organizations, E-P, undated (Box 30)
  - Constitution: Student organizations, R-Z, undated (Box 30)
  - Constitution: Student Union, undated (Box 30)
  - Constitution: U.S. National Student Association, 1979 August-1980 August (Box 30)
  - Constitution: Women's Student Government Association, undated (Box 30)
  - "Fusion" (newsletter), circa 1969 (Box 30)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa: minutes, circa 1955-1962 (Box 30)
  - Publications Board: agendas, announcements, etc., 1964-1969 (Box 30)
  - Publications Board: correspondence, circa 1963-1968 (Box 31)
  - Publications Board: correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 31)
  - Publications Board: minutes, 1958 May; 2 folders (Box 31)
  - Publications Board: minutes, 1969 October (Box 31)
  - Publications Board: minutes, 1971 September (Box 31)
  - Publications Board: reports, 1970-1978 (Box 32)
  - Report on Conduct Codes & Judicial System, 1969-1970 (Box 32)
  - Report: University of Miami Photojournalism in Workshop, 1965 October (Box 32)
  - Reports: Conduct Codes & Judicial System (materials from other institutions), 1969-1970; 2 folders (Box 32)
  - Reports: "History & Traditions" & other general reports, 1964-1964 (Box 32)
  - Reports: Housing Analyses, 1970-1972 (Box 32)
  - Reports: Study on the Needs of the Handicapped, 1975 August (Box 32)
  - Student Health Insurance, 1973-1979 (Box 32)
  - Student Health Insurance, 1977-1980 (Box 32)
  - Student Health Insurance: bids, 1974-1975 (Box 33)
  - Student Health Insurance: bids, 1975-1976 (Box 33)
  - Student Health Insurance: bids, 1979-1980 (Box 33)
  - Student organizations: officers, 1964-1970 (Box 33)
  - Student organizations: procedure for chartering, 1962 March 8-1966 March 16 (Box 33)
- Accession A86-76, 7
  This series includes materials from William Griffith's time as Vice President for Student Affairs. Files are partially alphabetical and include correspondence, reports, memorandums, printed materials, and other materials related to student housing, the Office of Minority Affairs, the Publications Board, the Chapel (including expansion and activities), student activities, the University Union administration and activities, materials related to racial and sex discrimination, and other topics. Included are the results of a survey administered to students on opinions about the Allen Building Takeover (called "Sit-In Study") as well as files on Title IX regulations and segregated facilities.
  - Student fees questionnaire, 1972 October (Box 36)
  - Academic Deans, Office of, 1974-1980 (Box 36)
  - Administrative Interns, Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - Administrative Interns, Projects, 1973-1973 (Box 36)
  - Admissions office: prospective students, 1973-1980 (Box 36)
  - Admissions, Planning/Policy (1 of 2), 1972-1980 (Box 36)
  - Admissions, Planning/Policy (2 of 2), 1972-1980 (Box 37)
  - Alumni Office: correspondence, 1971-1981; 2 folders (Box 37)
  - American Student Federation, 1979 (Box 37)
  - Bio-ethics, Students for Advancement of, 1978-1980 (Box 37)
  - Allied Arts of Durham, 1973-1974 (Box 37)
  - American Musical Theater, Proposed, 1977-1978 (Box 37)
  - Association of Duke Women, 1979-1981 (Box 37)
  - Bob Hope Show, 1978 (Box 37)
  - Bulletins of Duke University, Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 37)
  - Bursar, Office of, 1977-1979 (Box 37)
  - Bus Service, 1972-1979 (Box 37)
  - Business and Finance, 1975-1980 (Box 38)
  - Business Auxiliaries, 1974-1980 (Box 38)
  - Calendar Correspondence, 1969-1980 (Box 38)
  - Career Counseling, ad hoc committee on, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
  - Career Planning, Office of Coordinator, 1980 (Box 38)
  - Circle 'K', 1973-1978 (Box 38)
  - Class rings: Information, 1970 (Box 38)
  - Committee of Twelve, 1970 (Box 38)
  - Committee with NCCU/Duke, 1969-1970 (Box 38)
  - Conferences, 1969-1980 (Box 38)
  - Continuing Education, Office of, 1973-1978 (Box 38)
  - Cost Accounting, 1977-1978 (Box 38)
  - COSERV (National Council for Community Service to International Visitors), 1972 (Box 38)
  - Council of Deans, 1972-1973 (Box 38)
  - CAPS Advisory Committee (Counseling & Psychological Services), 1979 (Box 38)
  - Counseling Services, Ad hoc Committee on, 1976-1978 (Box 38)
  - Counseling Center, 1971-1977 (Box 38)
  - Cultural Affairs, Office of, 1970-1980; 2 folders (Box 39)
  - Duke Artists Series, 1970-1980 (Box 39)
  - Dean's Excuse for Students, 1972-1976
    RESTRICTED
  - Deferred Tuition Plan, 1971-1971 (Box 39)
  - Development Office, 1968-1980 (Box 39)
  - Dining Halls, Correspondence, 1969-1980 (Box 39)
  - Drama Committee, 1970-1980; 2 folders (Box 40)
  - Drama Committee, 1980 (Box 191)
    Personnel restriction until 2050
  - Duke Debate, 1971-1980 (Box 40)
  - Duke Endowment, 1976-1978 (Box 40)
  - Duke Summer Day Camp, 1975 (Box 40)
  - Educational Administration Advisory Group, 1970-1972 (Box 40)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1970-1980 (Box 40)
  - Federations: Baldwin, 1975-1983 (Box 40)
  - Federations: Edens, 1975-1976 (Box 41)
  - Federations: Few, 1979-1981 (Box 41)
  - Federations: Gilbert Addoms & Southgate, 1976-1977 (Box 41)
  - Federations: Kilgo, 1980 (Box 41)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration, 1980 (Box 41)
  - Financial Aid, 1967-1980 (Box 41)
  - Foreign Student Affairs Committee, 1973-1975 (Box 41)
  - Fraternities, 1974-1980 (Box 191)
  - Freewater Films, 1972-1980; 2 folders (Box 41)
  - Friday Luncheon Club, 1970-1982 (Box 41)
  - Graduate Student Association, 1973-1978 (Box 41)
  - Guns and Weapons Policy, 1970-1971 (Box 41)
  - Visitor: Professor Donald H. Smith, Study on Black Students admission & retention, 1979-1980 (Box 41)
  - Hassle House, 1978 (Box 41)
  - Health, Education & Welfare, Department of, 1970-1980 (Box 42)
  - Health, Education & Recreation, Department of, 1973-1980 (Box 42)
  - Hoof 'n'Horn, 1969-1980 (Box 42)
  - Housing, 1973-1980 (Box 42)
  - Housing: Central Campus Facility Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 42)
  - Housing: Damages in Dormitories, 1971-1980 (Box 42)
  - Housing: Central Campus, 1972-1980 (Box 43)
  - Housing: Dormitory Betterments Program, 1976-1978 (Box 43)
  - Housing: Association of Independent Houses, 1975-1980 (Box 43)
  - Housing: Graduate Center, 1971-1979 (Box 43)
  - Housing: House Dues, 1978-1979 (Box 43)
  - Housing: Information Sent to Students, 1976-1980; 2 folders (Box 43)
  - Housing: Proposals for Revised Housing Policy, 1977-1979 (Box 44)
  - Housing: Room Rates & Fees, 1975-1980 (Box 44)
  - Housing: Security Problems, 1975-1980 (Box 44)
  - Housing Statistics, 1974-1977 (Box 44)
  - Housing Statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 44)
  - Housing Statistics, 1978-1980 (Box 44)
  - Housing Management, Department of, 1975-1980 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, 1975-1980 (Box 44)
  - Human Resources, 1971-1980 (Box 45)
  - (Cameron) Indoor Stadium, 1974-1980 (Box 45)
  - Information Desk, 1970-1980 (Box 45)
  - Information Service, 1970-1980 (Box 45)
  - Institute of Policy Sciences, 1970-1980 (Box 45)
  - Duke University Insurance, 1975-1980 (Box 45)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1974-1980 (Box 45)
  - International House, 1971-1980 (Box 45)
  - Karate Club, 1973 (Box 45)
  - Law & Order Task Force Report, 1970 (Box 45)
  - Learning Experiences Survey, 1971 (Box 45)
  - Leash Regulations, 1970-1971 (Box 45)
  - Library, 1970-1980 (Box 45)
  - Mail & Package Delivery, 1973-1980 (Box 46)
  - Maintenance, 1970-1980 (Box 46)
  - Material Support Department, 1970-1980 (Box 46)
  - Minority Affairs, Office of, 1978-1980 (Box 46)
  - Minority Affairs, STP Program, 1975-1980 (Box 46)
  - Minority Affairs, STP-Program-Review (renamed to Minority Student Program Review), 1979-1980 (Box 46)
  - Minority Affairs, STP Advisory Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 46)
  - MIT/Duke Joint Telephone Meeting, 1975-1977 (Box 46)
  - Music: Department & Misc., 1972-1980 (Box 46)
  - Nova University, 1976-1982 (Box 46)
  - Nursing School, 1972-1983 (Box 47)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa (ODK), 1970-1980; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Orientation, Freshman, 1973-1980 (Box 47)
  - Page Auditorium, 1971-1980 (Box 47)
  - Panhellenic Council, 1978-1980 (Box 47)
  - Parents Weekend, 1977-1980 (Box 47)
  - Peace Corps, 1965-1976 (Box 47)
  - Performing Arts, Ad hoc Committee for, 1979 (Box 47)
  - Photography Club, 1971-1972 (Box 47)
  - Physical Planning Department, 1974 (Box 47)
  - Physical Plant, 1969-1980 (Box 48)
  - Placement Services, 1970-1980 (Box 48)